Guide to the Archives Union File (AUF), Section 10: Boxes 572-635
Archives Union File (AUF), Section 10: Boxes 572-635
- International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America, Publication (Box 604, Folder 4)
  - Item 17: Freight companies that want to sign 'interim' or 'me-too' agreements invited to meet with Teamsters National negotiating Committee on, 1994; Publication (Box 604, Folder 4)
  - Item 18: Freight companies that want to sign 'interim' or 'me-too' agreements invited to meet with Teamsters National negotiating Committee on, 1994; Publication (Box 604, Folder 4)
  - Item 19: Fifth largest TMI member, Carolina Freight, says that TMI's continued insistence on low-wage part-timers makes no sense, 1994; Publication (Box 604, Folder 4)
  - Item 20: Beware of disinformation, no matter its source, 1994; Publication (Box 604, Folder 4)
  - Item 21: Judge Edelstein rejects bid for temporary restraining order against Carey's proposal to revoke area conference charters, 1994; Publication (Box 604, Folder 4)
  - Item 22: Freight strike facts, 1994; Publication (Box 604, Folder 4)
  - Item 23: Effective strike leaves freight companies deply divided over bargaining strategy, 1994; Publication (Box 604, Folder 4)
  - Item 24: Fourth largest union freight carrier breaks ranks, signs agreement to accept national contract, 1994; Publication (Box 604, Folder 4)
  - Item 25: Freight strike to begin at midnight over campanies refusal to bargain in good faith, 1994; Publication (Box 604, Folder 4)
  - Item 26: How Time magazine slants its Carey coverage, 1994; Publication (Box 604, Folder 4)
  - Item 27: Teamsters say $3 million UPS settlement with OSHA on hazardous materials doesn't go far enough, 1994; Publication (Box 604, Folder 4)
  - Item 28: Teamsters call for national freight strike to begin, 1994; Publication (Box 604, Folder 4)
  - Item 29: Smear campaign continues against Ron Carey, 1994; Publication (Box 604, Folder 4)
  - Item 30: Statement by Teamsters General President Ron Carey about National Freight contract negotiations, 1994; Publication (Box 604, Folder 4)
  - Item 31: Teamsters Union moves to protect members' health, 1994; Publication (Box 604, Folder 4)
  - Item 32: Teamsters members who voted recently for reform candidates in local union elections voted against the dues increase, 1994; Publication (Box 604, Folder 4)
  - Item 33: Shea, Riley, Hogan, Cook kick in $600,000 of members' money to defend themselves in any litigation, 1994; Publication (Box 604, Folder 4)
  - Item 34: Vote on dues referendum is a strong mandate for major changes, 1994; Publication (Box 604, Folder 4)
  - Item 35: Workers win a victory over Pony Express, 1994; Publication (Box 604, Folder 4)
  - Item 36: International Union acts to prevent any looting of Union assets, 1994; Publication (Box 604, Folder 4)
  - Item 37: Teamster caravans roll across the country to protest freight industry's attack on the American dream, 1994; Publication (Box 604, Folder 4)
  - Item 38: Update on dues referendum, 1994; Publication (Box 604, Folder 4)
  - Item 39: Major new step for Teamster reform, 1994; Publication (Box 604, Folder 4)
  - Item 40: Facts about the four US area conferences, 1994; Publication (Box 604, Folder 4)
  - Item 41: Teamster members send message to freight companies, 1994; Publication (Box 604, Folder 4)
  - Item 42: Thousands of freight teamsters to take strike vote this weekend, 1994; Publication (Box 604, Folder 4)
  - Item 43: Labor Secretary offers new FMCS Director as Mediator to seek end to Teamster-Diamond Walnut dispute, 1994; Publication (Box 604, Folder 4)
  - Item 44: United Airlines workers lauch campaign seeking Teamster representation, 1994; Publication (Box 604, Folder 4)
  - Item 45: Teamster Union files claim against UPS, 1994; Publication (Box 604, Folder 4)
  - Item 46: Four Teamster Officials issue new disinformation, 1994; Publication (Box 604, Folder 4)
  - Item 47: Courts reject bid to delay membership vote on dues increase to fund strike benefits, 1994; Publication (Box 604, Folder 4)
  - Item 48: Statement by Ron Carey, Teamsters General Pres, 1994; Publication (Box 604, Folder 4)
  - Item 49: UPS Management agrees to remove safety hazard, 1994; Publication (Box 604, Folder 4)
  - Item 50: UPS out to break workers' backs teamsters threaten job action for., 1994; Publication (Box 604, Folder 4)
  - Item 51: The Policy Committee is being polled to approve the retaining as outside counsel the firm of, 1994; Publication (Box 604, Folder 4)
    Author: Eastern Conference Teamsters
  - Item 52: $100 Billion pension fund ripoff, 1981; Publication (Box 604, Folder 4)
    Notes: Article
  - Item 53: Justice Dept. vendetta against Michigan Steel haulers, 1994; Publication (Box 604, Folder 4)
  - Item 54: Teamsters chief rallies strikers, 1994; Publication (Box 604, Folder 4)
  - Item 55: 7 Trucking firms ask out of strike, 1994; Publication (Box 604, Folder 4)
  - Item 56: Dockhands urged to honor pickets, 1994; Publication (Box 604, Folder 4)
- International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America, Publication (Box 604, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Enclosed is a Fact Sheet for use in the REA Express election, 1965; Publication (Box 604, Folder 5)
    Author: Abraham Weiss
  - Item 2: REA Express, 1969; Publication (Box 604, Folder 5)
    Author: Frank E. Fitzsimmons
  - Item 3: REA Express Employees, Publication (Box 604, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Teamster Fact Sheet 4, 1968; Publication (Box 604, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Teamsters grow stronger BRC declining, Publication (Box 604, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: Teamsters grow stronger BRC declining, Publication (Box 604, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: Will You Lose Your Railroad Retirement If You Join the Teamsters?, Publication (Box 604, Folder 5)
  - Item 8: Put More Dollars In Your Pocket, Publication (Box 604, Folder 5)
  - Item 9: Fact or Fiction?, Publication (Box 604, Folder 5)
  - Item 10: The BRC Is Writing You Off, Publication (Box 604, Folder 5)
  - Item 11: The BRC: A Roadblock to Improved Railroad Retirement, Publication (Box 604, Folder 5)
  - Item 12: Some REA Employees in Chicago Received Pay Increases, Publication (Box 604, Folder 5)
  - Item 13: 12 Reasons to Vote Teamster, Publication (Box 604, Folder 5)
- International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America, Publication (Box 604, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Teamsters Sikorsky, 1961; Publication (Box 604, Folder 6)
    Author: Teamsters Sikorsky Organizing Committee
    Notes: v.1:no.12 (1961:June 15)
  - Item 2: Teamsters Sikorsky, 1961; Publication (Box 604, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.1:no.15 (1961:July 6)
  - Item 3: Teamsters Sikorsky, 1961; Publication (Box 604, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.1:no.16 (1961:July 12)
  - Item 4: Teamsters Sikorsky, 1961; Publication (Box 604, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.1:no.17 (1961:July 19)
  - Item 5: Teamsters Sikorsky, 1961; Publication (Box 604, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.1:no.18 (1961:July 21)
  - Item 6: Teamsters Sikorsky, 1961; Publication (Box 604, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.1:no.33 (1961:Oct. 27)
  - Item 7: Teamsters Sikorsky, 1961; Publication (Box 604, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.1:no.39 (1961:Nov. 17)
  - Item 8: Teamsters Sikorsky, 1961; Publication (Box 604, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.1:no.52 (1961:Dec. 19)
  - Item 9: Teamsters Sikorsky, 1962; Publication (Box 604, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.1:no.65 (1962:Mar. 13)
  - Item 10: Teamsters Sikorsky, 1962; Publication (Box 604, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.1:no.66 (1962:Mar. 14)
  - Item 11: Teamsters Sikorsky, 1962; Publication (Box 604, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.1:no.67 (1962:Mar. 15)
  - Item 12: Teamsters Sikorsky, 1962; Publication (Box 604, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.1:no.68 (1962:Mar. 16)
  - Item 13: Industrial Workers Swing to Teamsters, Publication (Box 604, Folder 6)
  - Item 14: Aberman Unveils Secret Weapon, 1961; Publication (Box 604, Folder 6)
  - Item 15: Teamsters Sikorsky, 1961; Publication (Box 604, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.1:no.5 (1961:Apr. 27)
  - Item 16: Teamsters Sikorsky, 1961; Publication (Box 604, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.1:no.6 (1961:May 4)
  - Item 17: Teamsters Sikorsky, 1961; Publication (Box 604, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.1:no.7 (1961:May 11)
  - Item 18: Teamsters Sikorsky, 1961; Publication (Box 604, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.1:no.8 (1961:May 18)
  - Item 19: Teamsters Sikorsky, 1961; Publication (Box 604, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.1:no.9 (1961:May 25)
  - Item 20: Teamsters Sikorsky, 1961; Publication (Box 604, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.1:no.10 (1961:June 1)
  - Item 21: Teamsters Sikorsky, 1961; Publication (Box 604, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.1:no.11 (1961:June 8)
- International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America, Publication (Box 604, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Go-Go Teamsters., Publication (Box 604, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: The US Government guaratees your secret ballot, Publication (Box 604, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: Hear Ye! Hear Ye! Compare Union, Publication (Box 604, Folder 7)
- International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America, Publication (Box 604, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Do you want Teamster Guarantees or voice promises?, Publication (Box 604, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: The VOICE of Truth, Publication (Box 604, Folder 8)
    Author: Teamsters Democratic Organizing Committee
  - Item 3: After the Egg-Heads, Do-Gooders, White-Collars and Sailor-Boys have shot their wad, Publication (Box 604, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: End the Sell-Out, Publication (Box 604, Folder 8)
  - Item 5: Your Right To Speak, Publication (Box 604, Folder 8)
  - Item 6: The National Labor Relations Board has ordered a second, Publication (Box 604, Folder 8)
  - Item 7: Do you want Teamster Guarantees or voice promises?, Publication (Box 604, Folder 8)
  - Item 8: Cast Your Vote For The Voice, Publication (Box 604, Folder 8)
- International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America, Publication (Box 604, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Safety & Health Facts, Publication (Box 604, Folder 9)
    Author: International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America. Safety and Health Department
  - Item 2: Safety & Health Facts, Publication (Box 604, Folder 9)
- International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America, Publication (Box 604, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Legislative Report - Oct. 29, 1984, Publication (Box 604, Folder 10)
  - Item 2: Now that your election for .Officers has been concluded, I wish to take this opportunity to advise you of the current position of the .teamsters, 1984; Publication (Box 604, Folder 10)
    Author: Jackie Presser
  - Item 3: Teamster 'Invitation' to White Collar Workers drafted by Eastern Conference - Your Office Employees Profession Organizaing Committee, Publication (Box 604, Folder 10)
  - Item 4: Teamster 'Invitation' to White Collar Workers drafted by Eastern Conference - Your Office Employees Profession Organizaing Committee, Publication (Box 604, Folder 10)
  - Item 5: Teamsters Are, Publication (Box 604, Folder 10)
  - Item 6: DRIVE (Democrat, Republican, Independetns, Voter Eduation), the political voice of the Teamsters, 1983; Publication (Box 604, Folder 10)
    Author: Jackie Presser; Ray Schoessling
  - Item 7: Legislative Report - congressional voting record - 98th Congress, Publication (Box 604, Folder 10)
  - Item 8: Major Contract changes and additional benefits that have been negotiated between the years 1936-1966 (Box 604, Folder 10)
  - Item 9: The Teamsters Union - its membership and structure its accomplishment for members, Publication (Box 604, Folder 10)
  - Item 10: The Teamsters Union - its membership and structure its accomplishment for members, Publication (Box 604, Folder 10)
    Notes: copy 2.
  - Item 11: New York State Teamsters Council: Legal Benefit Fund, 1984; Publication (Box 604, Folder 10)
    Author: New York State Teamsters Council
  - Item 12: New York State Teamsters Council: Legal Benefit Fund, 1984; Publication (Box 604, Folder 10)
  - Item 13: Panel Attorney Directory: Legal Benefit Fund, 1988; Publication (Box 604, Folder 10)
  - Item 14: Panel Attorney Directory: Legal Benefit Fund, 1988; Publication (Box 604, Folder 10)
  - Item 15: Teamster rank and file pension handbook, 1981; Publication (Box 604, Folder 10)
  - Item 16: Teamster rank and file pension handbook, 1981; Publication (Box 604, Folder 10)
  - Item 17: Steward's manual: a handbook for Teamster Stewards and Rank & File Activists, 1984; Publication (Box 604, Folder 10)
  - Item 18: How secure is your job?, Publication (Box 604, Folder 10)
  - Item 19: As you may already know, 400 workers, 1987; Publication (Box 604, Folder 10)
    Author: Franklin L. Gallegos
  - Item 20: Do you want to attend one of the most interesting and stimulating Social Events, 1987; Publication (Box 604, Folder 10)
    Author: Walter L. Johnson
  - Item 21: Update, 1982; Publication (Box 604, Folder 10)
    Author: Teamsters Local 732
  - Item 22: Union structure pyramid, Publication (Box 604, Folder 10)
- Teamsters for a Democratic Union, Publication (Box 604, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: The Vicious Circle, Publication (Box 604, Folder 11)
  - Item 2: Convention update, 1981; Publication (Box 604, Folder 11)
  - Item 3: Attend the rank and file convention, 1979; Publication (Box 604, Folder 11)
  - Item 4: Attend the rank and file convention, 1983; Publication (Box 604, Folder 11)
  - Item 5: Attend the rank and file convention, 1985; Publication (Box 604, Folder 11)
  - Item 6: TDU Constitution, Publication (Box 604, Folder 11)
  - Item 7: TDU Constitution, Publication (Box 604, Folder 11)
  - Item 8: Teamsters for a Democratic Union - 1979 Convention Program, Publication (Box 604, Folder 11)
  - Item 9: Teamsters for a Democratic Unon - 1981 Rank and File convention, Publication (Box 604, Folder 11)
  - Item 10: Teamsters for a Democratic Unon - 1981 Rank and File convention, Publication (Box 604, Folder 11)
  - Item 11: a cause worth truckin' for! Teamster for a Democratic Union organize for Rank and File Power - [constitution], 1976; Publication (Box 604, Folder 11)
  - Item 12: a cause worth truckin' for! Teamster for a Democratic Union organize for Rank and File Power - [constitution], 1976; Publication (Box 604, Folder 11)
- Teamsters for a Democratic Union, Publication (Box 604, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Convoy Contract Bulletin, 1976; Publication (Box 604, Folder 12)
    Notes: March 28, 1976.
  - Item 2: Convoy Contract Bulletin, 1978; Publication (Box 604, Folder 12)
    Notes: no.1 (1978:Dec.)
  - Item 3: Convoy Contract Bulletin, 1979; Publication (Box 604, Folder 12)
    Notes: no.2 (1979:Jan.)
  - Item 4: Convoy Contract Bulletin, 1979; Publication (Box 604, Folder 12)
    Notes: no.3 (1979:Feb.)
  - Item 5: Convoy Contract Bulletin, 1979; Publication (Box 604, Folder 12)
    Notes: no.4 (1979:Mar. 19)
  - Item 6: Convoy Contract Bulletin, 1979; Publication (Box 604, Folder 12)
    Notes: no.5 (1979:Mar. 21)
  - Item 7: Convoy Contract Bulletin, 1979; Publication (Box 604, Folder 12)
    Notes: no.6 (1979:Mar. 28)
  - Item 8: Convoy Contract Bulletin, 1979; Publication (Box 604, Folder 12)
    Notes: no.7 (1979:Apr. 2)
  - Item 9: Convoy Contract Bulletin, 1982; Publication (Box 604, Folder 12)
    Notes: no.2 (1982:Apr. 22)
  - Item 10: Convoy Contract Bulletin, 1982; Publication (Box 604, Folder 12)
    Notes: no.3 (1982:May 6)
  - Item 11: Convoy Contract Bulletin, 1982; Publication (Box 604, Folder 12)
    Notes: no.4 (1982:May 20)
  - Item 12: Convoy Contract Bulletin, 1982; Publication (Box 604, Folder 12)
    Notes: no.5 (1982:June 4)
  - Item 13: Convoy Contract Bulletin, 1982; Publication (Box 604, Folder 12)
    Notes: no.7 (1982:July 9)
  - Item 14: Convoy Contract Bulletin, 1984; Publication (Box 604, Folder 12)
    Notes: no.1 (1984:June 18)
  - Item 15: Convoy Contract Bulletin, 1985; Publication (Box 604, Folder 12)
    Notes: January 10, 1985.
  - Item 16: Convoy Contract Bulletin, 1985; Publication (Box 604, Folder 12)
    Notes: April 2, 1985.
  - Item 17: Convoy Contract Bulletin, 1985; Publication (Box 604, Folder 12)
    Notes: April 10, 1985.
  - Item 18: TDU Members Bulletin, 1982; Publication (Box 604, Folder 12)
    Notes: July 1982.
  - Item 19: Convoy Strike Bulletin, Publication (Box 604, Folder 12)
    Notes: no.2
  - Item 20: What counts is not what our enemies do but what we do in response, Publication (Box 604, Folder 12)
- Teamsters for a Democratic Union, Publication (Box 604, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: I want you to reform your unionjoin TDU, 1977; Publication (Box 604, Folder 13)
  - Item 2: TDU Organizers manual, Publication (Box 604, Folder 13)
  - Item 3: Running for office as TDU candidates, 1979; Publication (Box 604, Folder 13)
  - Item 4: Running for office as TDU candidates, 1979; Publication (Box 604, Folder 13)
  - Item 5: Organizing Teamsters on the job, 1979; Publication (Box 604, Folder 13)
  - Item 6: Organizing Teamsters on the job, 1979; Publication (Box 604, Folder 13)
  - Item 7: Organizing for a better contract: how you can make the difference, 1980; Publication (Box 604, Folder 13)
  - Item 8: Rank and file organizing at UPS, 1982; Publication (Box 604, Folder 13)
- Teamsters for a Democratic Union, Publication (Box 604, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Up Front, 1978; Publication (Box 604, Folder 14)
    Notes: v.1:no.1, 3-7, 9 (1978)
  - Item 2: Up Front, 1979; Publication (Box 604, Folder 14)
    Notes: v.2 (1979)
  - Item 3: Up Front, 1980; Publication (Box 604, Folder 14)
    Notes: v.2:no.1-5, 8 (1980)
  - Item 4: Up Front: Strike Special Edition, 1979; Publication (Box 604, Folder 14)
    Notes: no.1 (1979:Apr. 3) - no.8 (1979:Apr. 11)
  - Item 5: Up Front: Recession Special Edition, 1980-1981 (Box 604, Folder 14)
    Notes: no.1 (1980:July/Aug.) - no.4 (1981:Jan.)
- Teamsters for a Democratic Union, Publication (Box 605, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Vote for ..Local 375., Publication (Box 605, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: How to Workshops by Cornell University, Publication (Box 605, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Grocery contract comparison - Summer 1980, Publication (Box 605, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Speaking at Your Union Meeting, Publication (Box 605, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: First Annual Family Picnic, Publication (Box 605, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Join TDU, Publication (Box 605, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Organize for Rank and File Power - TDU Meeting, Publication (Box 605, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: We are having a meeting., Publication (Box 605, Folder 1)
    Notes: December 16.
  - Item 9: We are having a meeting., Publication (Box 605, Folder 1)
    Notes: September 14.
  - Item 10: Carhaulers.Majority Rule in '79, 1979; Publication (Box 605, Folder 1)
  - Item 11: Carhaulers.Buffalo Meeting, 1979; Publication (Box 605, Folder 1)
  - Item 12: Carhaulers.It's The Time of Decision, Publication (Box 605, Folder 1)
  - Item 13: Carhaulers.Don't Forget, 1979; Publication (Box 605, Folder 1)
  - Item 14: UP FRONT Local 375 Election Special Edition, Publication (Box 605, Folder 1)
    Notes: no.1
  - Item 15: UP FRONT Local 375 Election Special Edition, Publication (Box 605, Folder 1)
    Notes: no.3
  - Item 16: UP FRONT Local 375 Election Special Edition, Publication (Box 605, Folder 1)
    Notes: no.4
  - Item 17: UP FRONT Local 375 Election Special Edition, Publication (Box 605, Folder 1)
    Notes: no.5
  - Item 18: UP FRONT Local 375 Election Special Edition, Publication (Box 605, Folder 1)
  - Item 19: National Master Freight Agreement, National Contract for UPS, National Contract for Carhaulers, 1979; Publication (Box 605, Folder 1)
  - Item 20: Teamsters Local 449 and National Automobile Transporters Agreement, 1979; Publication (Box 605, Folder 1)
  - Item 21: Teamsters Local 375 and National Master Freight Agreement, 1979; Publication (Box 605, Folder 1)
  - Item 22: Pete Camarata.Local 299, Detroit, 1977; Publication (Box 605, Folder 1)
  - Item 23: Big R's Bull Sheet, 1980; Publication (Box 605, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.1:no.1 (1980:June)
  - Item 24: Big R's Bull Sheet, 1980; Publication (Box 605, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.1:no.2 (1980:July)
  - Item 25: Big R's Bull Sheet, 1980; Publication (Box 605, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.1:no.3 (1980:Aug./Sep.)
  - Item 26: Big R's Bull Sheet, 1980; Publication (Box 605, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.1:no.4 (1980:Oct.)
  - Item 27: Roadway's Profits Up, Publication (Box 605, Folder 1)
  - Item 28: Vote for Stan Markiewicz, 1979; Publication (Box 605, Folder 1)
  - Item 29: Draw the Line in '79, 1979; Publication (Box 605, Folder 1)
  - Item 30: Second: Because less than .5% of Local 375 members, 1979; Publication (Box 605, Folder 1)
- Teamsters for a Democratic Union, Publication (Box 605, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Teamsters for Democratic Union: 12th Annual Rank & File Convention, 1987; Publication (Box 605, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Spying on your employera guide to Researching your employer in your Local Public Library, 1979; Publication (Box 605, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Teamsters for Democracy, Publication (Box 605, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: The Teamsters dissidents mobilize, 1977; Publication (Box 605, Folder 2)
    Author: Robert H. Holden
    Notes: Photocopy from The Nation, November 5, 1977.
  - Item 5: Transforming the Teamsters, 1976; Publication (Box 605, Folder 2)
    Author: Jerry Bornstein
    Notes: Photocopy from The Progressive, December 1976.
  - Item 6: Carhaul Contract Bulletin: More progress is needed, and can be won: significant gains forced by strike (August 16, 1985), Publication (Box 605, Folder 2)
    Notes: August 16, 1985.
  - Item 7: Carhaul Contract Bulletin: Only unity will win a decent contract (July 24, 1985), Publication (Box 605, Folder 2)
    Notes: July 24, 1985.
  - Item 8: UPS Rank & File Contract News, 1987; Publication (Box 605, Folder 2)
    Notes: May 29, 1987.
  - Item 9: A comparison of supplements to the National Master Freight Agreement, September 1978, Publication (Box 605, Folder 2)
  - Item 10: Rebuilding the labor movement at the grass roots: Teamsters for a Democratic Union, Publication (Box 605, Folder 2)
  - Item 11: How to make your local by-laws more democratic: including rank & file model by-laws, 1978; Publication (Box 605, Folder 2)
  - Item 12: Getting the most from your grievance procedure, 1979; Publication (Box 605, Folder 2)
  - Item 13: Getting the most from your grievance procedure, 1977; Publication (Box 605, Folder 2)
  - Item 14: Getting the most from your grievance procedure, 1977; Publication (Box 605, Folder 2)
  - Item 15: How to make your Local by-laws more democratic, Publication (Box 605, Folder 2)
  - Item 16: How to make your Local by-laws more democratic, Publication (Box 605, Folder 2)
  - Item 17: Getting the most from your grievance procedure, 1984; Publication (Box 605, Folder 2)
  - Item 18: The Attack on Teamsters in the grocery industry: how to turn the tide, 1979; Publication (Box 605, Folder 2)
- International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America, Publication (Box 605, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Freedom of speech or Freedom to slander?, Publication (Box 605, Folder 3)
    Author: 3M Revere In-Plant Organizing Committee
  - Item 2: Insurance program very inadequategives no surgical benefits for employees., Publication (Box 605, Folder 3)
    Author: F.M. Stamper Hospital
  - Item 3: Do You Want to be a Soldier in the Fight Against the United States?, 1961; Publication (Box 605, Folder 3)
    Author: Esquire
  - Item 4: Union Membership Test, 1963; Publication (Box 605, Folder 3)
    Author: The Specialty Worker
  - Item 5: Do you know? What Foremen and Supervisors cannot do, Publication (Box 605, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: Union Steward fired, Publication (Box 605, Folder 3)